# Or Zarhi

## Full-Stack Developer

#### **About Me**

I am an experienced software developer with 1.5 years of experience in the industry and a deep passion for programming. Throughout my career, I'm always looking for ways to improve my skills and stay on top of the latest technologies.

## **Experience**

#### **Full-Stack Developer**

Maxsoft company

Aug 2022 to present

A Full Stack developer at a professional software company. Worked on several projects for various customers. Developed and maintained code with assorted tools, such as: Node.js, .net, mongoDB, Sql, JavaScript and React.

#### **Computer Science Tutor**

Zefat College
Jan 2023 to present

Teaching C#, Data structures and Algorithms courses.

<u>Letter of recommendation</u>

#### **Full-Stack Developer**

Codeo company
Jan 2022 to Jul 2022

I worked as Full Stack Developer.
I developed and maintained code. I had the chance to work with: Node.js, .net,
JavaScript and React.

## **Education**

#### **Kinneret College**

Nov 2019 to Jun 2023

## **Practical Software Engineer Student**

93 GPA

## **Skills**

Node.js, Express.js, NoSQL, React, Remix, Tailwind

## **Military Service**

#### **Division 319**

Feb 2016 to Oct 2018

I managed other soldiers, took care of orders and supplies.

## **Contact**

**1** 052-363-8638

in www.linkedin.com/in/or-zarhi

or.zarhi11@gmail.com

m http

https://github.com/orzarhi